Kettle and Idols
Yes, well, it's early and we're talking about the ending.
I didn't try to talk about anime and manga yet.
That's right.
Now that we're here, please introduce some news from Chizuran. Please do.
August 11, Friday, a national holiday.
There will be Atsuo Inari's anniversary event at Lina World Plaza Stage in Yamagata Prefecture.
It is the 8th anniversary of his birth and spread.
Please give us your best regards.
What kind of event is it going to be?
Yes, it will be. Every year, Atsuo Inari's anniversary event is very loose,
I think it will be an event that even newcomers can enjoy together.
Yes, it will be. Thank you very much.
Well then, everyone please look forward to going to the Yamagata Prefecture Hanami App. Best regards.
Please give my best regards.
Please continue.
October 29, Sunday, Staple Idol Festival at Yokohama Arena.
Oku Iidaido will perform at the Autumn New Music Harvest Festival.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. Iida Ido Oku-san, shining Cinderella group at the last Stapler Idol Fest ,
After that, from the three of us, and also from All Death Nippon,
You also did the "Zero" show,
I know you must have been busy,
This time, all groups will perform their first song, or at least one new song.
Yes.
Do you have any thoughts about the team or something?
Yes, we do.
We don't know what new song we will perform yet,
We are very excited about it.
I am also looking forward to hearing other groups' new songs.
Also, I'm sure you'll be interacting with members of various groups behind the scenes.
Do you want to be friends with anyone?
Ehhhhh...
But Chilia and I got to know each other well at the last Stapler Festival,
I want to deepen our friendship. I want to get to know her better.
I'll be updating my Instagram after the concert, so I hope everyone can look forward to it.We will be updating the instagram after the concert, so I hope everyone will look forward to it.
Yes.
Yes. One more thing.
Please give us a big introduction.
And on Friday, December 29th, at the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall,
We are going to hold the curtain-raiser for "The Legend of Iginari" at the Pacifico Yokohama National Grand Hall on Friday, December 29th.
I definitely want you to come.
Yes, I do. Yes, I'm sure you do.
Congratulations.
It's a big live concert at the end of the year.
How do you feel now?
That's a very easy question.
But it's also the subtitle,
"The Legend of Iginari Begins", so please don't miss the moment when the legend begins,
So please don't miss the moment when the legend begins.
It's the end of the year. Please open your hands while you still can,
I hope you will come and visit us.
I look forward to seeing you all.
Thank you very much.
Last but not least, I, Kettle-kun, present you with a cup of tea to cheer you up.
Thank you, kettle.
It looks hot.
I'll have some.
Delicious.
This time it's a blend of herbal teas to soothe your throat.
Herb tea. It smells like herbs.
Delicious. It is refreshing and very tasty.
Thank you very much. I didn't get any cute reactions,
I'm sure everyone is satisfied with this.
Now, please give us a cute closing remark.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you all very much for watching this far.
I will do my best so that I can participate again.
Bye bye!
This program is sponsored by
Mr. Yukakko Ryu
Mr. YamauchiMr. Yamauchi
Mr. Fukubayashi
Mr. Dirk
Mr. Koji Koji
Thank you very much for your kind attention!
We look forward to seeing you all again!